[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":37363,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":93658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":18693,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":112352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4181,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":116535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1214,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":117750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":121223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1094,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":122318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":125711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1159,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":126870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":129290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":917,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":130208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":132314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6< /sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1666,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":133981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":136456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1038,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":137495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br />< br /> (R emember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3032,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":140527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":787,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":141315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":143441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1445,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":144886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":147037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1736,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":148773,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":151050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":970,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":152021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13690,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":165713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse  under + <sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":44010,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":209725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":213250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1089,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":214340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":216562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":901,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":217463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":222986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":876,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":223864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":226174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub >6</sub> .","rt":833,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":227008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":230675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":231618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be per formed s tarting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":25009,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":256627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but  there i s no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":59374,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":316002,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":322580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7516,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":330097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Rememb er, a ge nerator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":334366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":26742,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":361108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":16135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":377243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":8952,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":386196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":393055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":6054,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":399110,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedba ck to ma ke sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":16705,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":415815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":419797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1321,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":421119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":423571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2585,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":426156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":428585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":431105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4050,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":435156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":9027,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":444183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it's less than 9, no subtraction is needed. ","explanation_history":["4 plus 1 equals 5, and w","4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it's be","4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it's b","4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it's ","4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it'sl","4 plus 1 equals 5, and since it's less than 9, no subtraction is needed. "],"response_history":["5"],"rt":22165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":466348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8 + 4 = 12. 12 is greater than 9, therefore must subtract 9, which = 3","explanation_history":["8 -","8 =  ","8 =","8 + 4 +","8 + 4 = 12. 12 is greater than 9, therefore must subtract 9, which = 3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":26045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":492394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1","explain":true,"explanation":"1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 9 = 1, 1+8=0, this is true for all numbers 0-9","explanation_history":["`","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 =","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 + ","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 +","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 = ","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 =","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 ","1 can be used to get all other numbers , such t hat 1 + 0","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0 ","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 0","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 9=","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 9 = 1, 1=","1 can be used to get all other numbers, such that 1 + 9 = 1, 1+8=0, this is true for all numbers 0-9"],"response_history":["1"],"rt":105822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":598216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":47330,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":645547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":19598,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":665146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":4300,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":669447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"it's the number that is used to equal the identity. ","explanation_history":["it's th","it's the number that is used to eu","it's  the numb er that is used to equal the identify","it's the number that is used to equal the identif","it's the number that is used to equal the identity. "],"response_history":["6"],"rt":31593,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":701041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"not sure. ","explanation_history":["nt","nt","not sure. "],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":33938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":734980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"don't remember","explanation_history":["don't e","don't remember"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":742169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"not sure","explanation_history":["not sure"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":27289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":769459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"not sure","explanation_history":["not sure"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6409,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":775869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":8205,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":784076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+n -1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["=","+n  -","+n  ","+n -1"],"rt":86440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":870516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an elem ent x un der +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"+n - x","explain":true,"explanation":"not sure","explanation_history":["not sure"],"response_history":["=","+n - x"],"rt":37025,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":907541,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"not sure if there is a pattern","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["you could ","not sure if there is a pattern"],"rt":27464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":935006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an  odd num ber, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":6793,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":941800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":3153,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":944953,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Tru e","Fals e"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":9529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":954483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may or may not be a divisor of n","explanation_history":["If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even. ","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even.","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, which should be divisble ","If generators are only od d number s, and x is not a generator it must be even, which should be divi","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, whi","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, wh","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, wm","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, w","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may oor ","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may oor","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may oor ","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may oor","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may oo","If generators are only odd numbers, and x is not a generator it must be even, may or may not be a divisor of n"],"response_history":["True","False"],"rt":62204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1016687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11720,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1028408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"It might be a generator , not su re though. ","explanation_history":["It might be a generator, not sure htough.","It might be a generator, not sure htough","It might be a generator, not sure htoug","It might be a generator, not sure htou","It might be a generator, not sure hto","It might be a generator, not sure ht","It might be a generator, not sure h","It might be a generator, not sure though. "],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":18421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1046830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":26758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1073588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1828,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1075416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"26","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["26"],"rt":3165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1078581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1081063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College level statistics, pre-calculus. ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Statistics ","College level statistics ","College level statistics, pre-calculus. "],"rt":18299,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1099363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but  not ofte n or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4706,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1104070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":3587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1107658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":" Do you f eel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1110549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1114370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1117017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2617,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1119635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":2969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1122605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1125317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was very interesting, although I wish there was a chance to review concepts throughout the main task of answering questions, to re-familiarize myself with the concepts. ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["This was very interesting, although I wish there was ach","This was very interesting, although I wish there was ac","This was very interesting, although I wish there was a","This was very interesting, altho ugh I wi sh there was  ","This was very interesting, although I wish there was a chance to review concepts througout the ","This was very interesting, although I wish there was a chance to review concepts througou","This was very interesting, although I wish there was a chance to review concepts througo","This was very interesting, although I wish there was a chance to review concepts throughout the main task of answering questions, to re-familiarize myself with the concepts. "],"rt":40744,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1166061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]